<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>centurylink on Luke's blog site</title><link>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/tags/centurylink/</link><description>Recent content in centurylink on Luke's blog site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 20:48:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/tags/centurylink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ubiquiti - Configuring an EdgeRouter X to Replace a CenturyLink Router - Zyxel C3000Z</title><link>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/posts/ubiquiti-configuring-an-edgerouter-x-to-replace-a-centurylink-router-c3000z/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 20:48:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/posts/ubiquiti-configuring-an-edgerouter-x-to-replace-a-centurylink-router-c3000z/</guid><description>Bypassing another bad CenturyLink router. This time, I have the Zyxel C3000Z which I need in order to get the bonded pair for the fastest DSL I can get in my area. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m old fashioned, but 80MB is plenty for our household&amp;rsquo;s needs.
We won&amp;rsquo;t actually be able to get rid of this device completely, but we can disable all of it&amp;rsquo;s functionality and allow it to pass through data to the EdgeRouter.</description></item><item><title>Ubiquiti - Getting Rid of the CenturyLink Router</title><link>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/posts/ubiquiti-getting-rid-of-the-centurylink-router/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 22:17:05 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/posts/ubiquiti-getting-rid-of-the-centurylink-router/</guid><description>Getting Rid of the CenturyLink Router When CenturyLink (CL) installed Fiber-To-The-Home (FTTH) with Prism service, they also required the use of their router/modem. I learned to hate this junky device with wi-fi issues and intermittent connection problems. Luckily, the modem of this device was not used. The modem was locked up in the access box outside.
Looking at the back of the Technicolor C2000T, the WAN port was connected by a regular Cat 5e cable, indicating that there was no need for the purchase of a fiber-modem.</description></item><item><title>Ubiquiti - Configuring an EdgeRouter X to Replace a CenturyLink Router</title><link>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/posts/ubiquiti-configuring-an-edgerouter-x-to-replace-a-centurylink-router/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 22:16:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://blog.lukebtaylor.com/posts/ubiquiti-configuring-an-edgerouter-x-to-replace-a-centurylink-router/</guid><description>Previously, I discussed various options when considering the replacement of a CenturyLink Technicolor C2000T router/modem in Getting Rid of the CenturyLink Router.
Time to get rid of the CenturyLink router. With the Ubiquiti EdgeRouter X plugged in, and the eth1 port hooked up to my laptop&amp;rsquo;s LAN port, getting to the login was easy enough.
In the Windows Network and Sharing Center, I selected the ethernet adapter&amp;rsquo;s properties and gave it a static IP of 192.</description></item></channel></rss>